你还好吗
Are you okay?
12小时前
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：小松狮    Silmar    夜    诺米    nana
时间轴：虫不知    傻蛐蛐     特效：Will
■
校对：小路      后期：冰河       监制：蛐蛐
-你简直是救命恩人  -是啊  伙计
- You are a life saver.  - Yeah, man.
-我们实在太感激你了  -太感谢了
- We can't thank you enough.  - Hey, mad props.
我发誓那人说的是往南面开
I could have sworn the guy said south.
但是突然一下我们就离开了大路
But then, all of a sudden we're off the main road.
我想边开车边看地图
I'm trying to read the map while I'm driving,
实在是个愚蠢的行为
which is a bonehead maneuver.
忽然"砰"的一声  我们就掉进了沟里
And all of a sudden... Bang, we're in that ditch.
对 "砰"  我还搞不清楚发生了什么
Yeah, bam, I'm like, what the hell? You know?
对了  还有我的咖啡杯
Yes, and my coffee mug.
咖啡  我的咖啡杯
Coffee? My mug of coffee?
全洒在我裤子上  简直就是恶梦
It spills all over my pants. I mean, just... a nightmare.
伙计  说真的  你该装个GPS导航仪
Dude, you so need GPS. I mean, for real.
就像我说的
Like I said,
我们对你感激涕零
we couldn't be more grateful.
难道就不能把他们扔这儿吗
Can't we just dump them here?
什么  等着别人发现他们吗
What, then somebody finds them?
那时怎么办  已经有人看见我们了
Then what? People have seen us.
你得把车子沉到河里  伙计
You're gonna flood it, man.
我不会把车沉到河里的  它不能沉  懂吗
I'm not gonna flood it. She's not going to flood, all right?
我们得乐观点  明白吗
We're just gonna stay positive, right?
我们要收拾好这烂摊子  希望能发动起来
We're going to clean up this mess. Wish you would start.
该死的  看见没  她已经进过水了
Damn it. See? You flooded it.
好吧  好吧  你知道吗
All right. All right. You know what?
车子会发动起来的
The RV is going to start now.
车子会马上发动起来的
The RV is going to start right now.
发动起来以后
It's gonna start and we're gonna
我们就开去你家
drive it over to your house.
我们把它开过去停一个晚上
We're gonna drive it over there and park it overnight.
-然后明天一早  -不行  不能去我家
- And then tomorrow...  - No, man, not my house!
闭嘴
Shut up!
收拾好这烂摊子后
After we finish cleaning up this mess,
你走你的阳关道  我过我的独木桥
We will go our separate ways.
从此井水不犯河水
Our paths will never cross.
天知地知你知我知
And we will tell this to no one.
明白吗
Understood?
我现在能说话了吗
What, I can talk now?
好吧
Fine.
你都已经替我说完了
That goes double for me.
很好  争气点
Okay, okay. Be good to me.
成了
Yes!
很好  很棒
Yes, ok, ok.
该死
Oh, shit.
绝
命
毒
师
第一季
第二集
沃尔特
Walt?
你出来吗
You coming out?
当然
Yeah, absolutely.
想听趣事吗
You wanna hear something funny?
上周四  我们开了教工大会
We had a faculty meeting last thursday
内容有关毕业生留影
And the topic was senior class photos,
去年我们定了新规定
and how we had instituted a new rule last year
允许毕业生
that seniors are allowed to
选择喜欢的摄影师来拍摄毕业照
have photos taken by a photographer of their choice,
不一定
you know, not necessarily
用学校雇的摄影师
the photographer that the school hires.
所以
That's so --
总之  有些毕业班的女生们
So, anyway, some of the senior girls
前往
were going to that...
高级的摄影棚拍毕业照
glamour shots place, to have their photos taken,
结果等她们拿来了所有照片
and now they're bringing us all these photos,
琼· 埃普曼  你认识的
and Joan Epperman, you know Joan,
突然发现照片都拍出她们乳沟了
suddenly has to go through all these photos
所以得仔细检查  然后退回去
and turn them down, because they show cleavage.
亲爱的  还要薄饼吗
Did you get enough pancakes, sweetie?
不用了  我饱了
Yeah. I'm good.
甚至那些平胸的姑娘  都有乳沟
You know, even these small-busted girls... have cleavage.
很明显  现在有种新型的胸罩
Apparently there's some new type of brassiere,
或是别的玩意
or something.
神奇胸罩
The wonderbra...
那叫神奇胸罩
It's the wonderbra.
是吗  好的
Yeah? OK.
你好  这里是沃尔特  斯凯勒和小沃尔特的家
Hey, there. You've reached Walt, Skyler and Walter Junior.
我们现在不能接电话
We can't come to the phone right now,
请留言
so please leave us a message.
你好  怀特先生  这里是美国电话电报公司
Hello, Mr. White. This is AT&T calling.
您对您现在的长途电话服务满意吗
Are you happy with your current long distance service?
如果您不满意  我将会
'Cause if you're not, I would definitely, really really
很乐意尽快与您联络
love to talk to you as soon as possible about...
你好  我是沃尔特·怀特
Hello? Hello, hello. This is Walter White speaking.
你不是说他已经死了吗
You said he was practically dead, okay?
你还说他马上就会死
You said he would die any minute!
听着  我正在和我的家人吃早餐
Listen, I am having breakfast with my family right now,
我真的不太喜欢这些推销电话
and I really don't appreciate these sales calls.
太糟糕了  伙计  猜猜发生了什么
Well, too bad, man, 'cause guess what.
他还没死
He's still not dead!
我把耳朵贴在车上  就能听到
I went and put my ear to the RV, I can hear him, like,
他在里面滚来滚去的声音
rolling around in there, all right?
我想他醒了  大概想要松绑
I think he's awake, man. I think he's trying to get loose.
你到底在哪里  我在这里快疯了
Where the hell are you? I'm freaking out over here!
-该死的 冷静下来  -你会帮我收拾残局吗
- Calm down, damn it.  - Are you gonna help me clean this up?
-这事还没完呢  -冷静
- We've got loose ends here!  - Calm down!
放学以后我会过去的
I will be there after school.
放学后  你在敷衍我吗
After school? Are you shitting me?
别上班了  打电话请假
Ditch it, man, call in sick.
听着  对我说什么都没用
Listen, that is just not going to work for me.
我完全不感兴趣
I'm not interested in that at all.
希望你不要再打来了
And I would appreciate if you don't call here anymore.
可恶  这些人可真是烦
Damn. They're so annoying, those people.
-过得开心  宝贝  -好的  妈妈  你也一样
- You have a good day, sweetie.  - Okay, mom, you too.
再见  亲爱的
Bye, honey.
-开车当心点  -好的
- Drive safe.  - Okay.
唷  唷  唷  148-3369
Yo, yo, yo, 148-3369,
代表阿尔布开克
representing the ABQ.
何事  贱人
What up, biatch?
提示音后留话
Leave it at the tone.
"手性"这个术语
So, the term "chiral"
来源于希腊语的"手"
derives from the Greek word "hand".
它在化学中的概念是  就如同你的左手
And the concept here being that, just as your left hand,
和你的右手互为镜像
and your right hand are mirror images of one another, right?
相同而又对立
Identical, and yet opposite.
所以  有机化合物
Well, so too organic compounds can exist as
总是以互为镜像的形式
mirror image forms
存在于分子水平上
of one another all the way down at the molecular level.
虽然看似相似
But although they may look the same,
但是生物活性不尽相同
they don't always behave the same.
比如说
For instance...
抱歉  比如说
I'm sorry... for instance...
酞胺哌啶酮[镇静剂]
Thalidomide.
这种药物的右旋异构体
The right-handed isomer of the drug thalidomide
是一种很有效的药物
is a perfectly fine good medicine
用于减轻
to give to a pregnant woman
孕妇晨吐的症状  但是
to prevent morning sickness. But,
如果给孕妇错服了
make the mistake of giving that same pregnant woman
酞咪脈啶酮的左旋异构体
the left-handed isomer of the drug thalidomide,
那么她生出的婴儿
and her child will be born with
将会严重畸形
horrible birth defects.
此等事件曾在上个世纪50年代发生过
Which is precisely what happened in the 1950s.
那么  手性的  手性
So, chiral, chirality,
镜像  懂了吗
mirrored images, right?
一个有活性  一个没有活性
Active, inactive.
一好一坏
Good, bad.
本  请讲
Yes, Ben?
这个会出现在凶杀案里吗
Is this gonna be on the murder?
什么
What?
期中考试会考吗(沃尔特听错了)
Is this gonna be on the mid-term?
期中考试会不会考手性  不会  也许
The chirality on the mid-term? No, no, well, maybe,
也许会  对
maybe, yes, you know, but prepare
要做好出现在期中考里的准备
for it to be on the mid-term.
多知道一点也没损失  不是吗
Can't hurt to know it, right?
知识就是力量
Knowledge is power!
不  不
Oh, no, no...
不妙了  不妙了
Not good. Not good.
怎么
What the...
你  你
Hey, hey, you, you, hey.
听着  别  别  别
Listen... No, no, no, no!
上帝啊
Oh, God!
辣妈性爱
MILF's?
辣妈性爱是什么鬼东西
What the hell is a MILF?
现在怎么办
Now what?
另一个  在车里的  他
The other one, out in the RV, he's...
-你确定  -是的
- You're sure?  - Yes.
-不然你自己去看好了  -对  真是个好主意
- You know what, feel free to go check it yourself.  - Yes, good idea.
也许我该在他晃悠到大街上之前
Maybe I should do that before he
亲自去察看一下
do wanders off down the damn street.
-你知道吗  我  -行了  行了
- Okay, you know what, I...  - All right, all right!
楼下的那位  说说他的情况
The one downstairs, tell me about him.
快点  什么都可以  说点什么
Come on, anything, something!
-至少可以先说名字  -疯狂小八
- Start with his name, at least!  - Krazy-8.
疯狂小八  这到底什么鬼意思
Krazy-8? What the hell does that even mean?
我不知道好吗  他就像个疯子
I don't know, man, okay? I mean, he's like,
行了吗  我也不知道
Krazy-8, okay? I don't know.
那你经常跟他合伙吗
So, you work with him regularly?
不  跟他合作得不多
No, not him so much.
-主要是跟他表弟  -他表弟是谁
- His cousin, mainly.  - Who's his cousin?
-车里的那个  -行了  行了
- The guy out in the RV!  - All right, all right.
疯狂小八比他高一等级
Krazy-8's one level higher.
高一等级
One level higher?
对  不是街头混混水平
Yeah, you know, not like street level.
更高一级
Higher.
就好比到处都有星巴克
You know, there's like a starbucks at every corner?
疯狂小八  就是卖给星巴克咖啡豆的人
Krazy-8 is, like, the dude that sells starbucks his beans.
好吧  所以他算经销商
Okay, so he's a distributor.
好吧  那么  他
Okay, so, is he...
我是说  他是不是  换句话说
I mean, is he... in other words...
他是不是暴力狂
What is his reputation for violence?
这个
Well, um...
他昨天想要杀了我们  所以应该是吧
He did try to kill us both yesterday, so there's that.
我想说的是  他是个经销商  对吧
What I'm trying to say is that he's a distributor, right?
他是  他是商人  生意人
He's a... He's a businessman, he's a man of business.
也就是说
It would therefore seem to follow
他可能不会
that he is capable of acting
表现地那么狭隘  对吗
out of mutual self-interest, yes?
什么
What?
你觉得他这个人
Do you think he is capable
听得进道理吗
of listening to reason?
什么道理
What kind of reason?
像是  亲爱的疯狂小八  听好
You mean like "Dear krazy-8, listen,
如果我放你走  你能保证
if I let you go, will you promise not
不回来杀我全家
to come back and waste my entire family,
不砍我脑袋  你是说这种道理吗
no colombian neckties." you mean that kind of reason?
不  伙计  我可不敢说
No, man, I can't say as I have
我他妈的对他寄予如此大的厚望
high fuck hopes as that concern.
什么声音
What was that?
怎么了
What was what?
来看啊
Come!
我们得把他绑起来
We gotta tie him up.
咱们刚刚怎么没绑着他呢
Why the hell didn't we tie him up?
因为他昏过去了
Because he was out cold.
可要是他是装的呢
But what if he's faking it?
换做是我  肯定会装成给打晕了
Like if it was me, I'd be all faking being knocked out, yo!
然后  等到危险过去了
And then, when the coast is clear,
再起来找武器
I'd be up looking for weapons and shit,
等机会突袭
waiting to pounce!
如果现在换做是我
Now if it was me, and I couldn't
找不到件称心的武器
find a decent like weapon
我就会躺回去  再等时机
I would just lie back down, and bide my time.
那我们现在做什么
So now what do we do?
你老问我
You keep asking me that
好像我心里有底似的
like you think I have some answer.
-你总得做点什么吧  -是我们
- Well, you gotta do something! - We!
我们得做点什么  我愿意听听你的建议
We have got to do something, and I am opened to suggestions.
伙计  整件事都是你搞出来的
Man, uh-uh, okay, this whole thing was your deal!
你怎么能赖到我头上呢
Don't you dare put that on me!
是你把这些人带出来
You brought those guys out there,
全是你的错
this is your responsibility.
说的像是我找到你  求着给你制毒似的
Like I came to you, begging to cook meth.
像我跟你说  书呆子老伙计啊
"Nerdiest old dude I know,
你想来做点儿纯冰毒吧
you wanna come cook crystal please."
我得问问我那穿着纸尿裤的奶奶
"I'd ask my diaper-wearing granny,
可是她的轮椅进不了旅行车
but her wheelchair wouldn't fit in the RV."
那气化磷酸盐怎么办
What about the... the phosphate gas?
气化磷酸盐  怎么了
Phosphine gas. What about it?
我是说  你觉得气化磷酸盐还可能杀死他吗
I mean, do you think it still might kill him?
比如延迟反应之类的
You know, with like a delayed reaction or something?
我不清楚
I don't know.
-你可是个科学家啊  -听着
- You're supposed to be a scientist! - Look!
这不是我们现在该考虑的
This isn't even the issue that demands immediate attention.
旅行车里还有具尸体呢
We have got a body in that RV,
天气开始变得炎热  明白我意思吗
and it's getting warmer outside, understand?
我们得赶快采取行动
And we have got to do something about that soon.
用某种方法使得人不知鬼不觉
And in a way that no one will ever find it.
最后我要说的
Now that last part
非常  非常重要
is very, very important.
那就是
Therefore,
我们的最佳策略
it seems to me that our best course of action
应该是化学消融法
would be chemical disincorporation.
让他在强酸里溶解掉
Dissolving in strong acid.
伙计  我有点混乱
Oh man, that's messed up.
你不是  你不是说真的吧
You're not... you're not serious?
你说真的
You're serious?
谁来动手
Who's gonna do that?
别看我
And don't look at me!
我猜咱俩得一起干
I guess we'll both do it together.
不行  怀特先生  我搞不定尸体
No, Mr. White, okay, I'm not good with dead bodies.
咱俩是拴在一条绳上的蚂蚱  懂吗
We're in this 50/50, okay?
我猜还有一个公平的办法
I guess the only other fair way
那就是
to go about this would be...
其中一人去处理
That one of us deals with the...
尸体的问题  另外一个去
body situation, while the other one of us...
处理疯狂小八那事儿
deals with the Krazy-8 situation.
事已至此
In a scenario like this,
我想  除了抛硬币
I don't suppose it is bad form to just...
也别无他法了
flip a coin.
-猜正反  -我去用酸处理尸体  好吧
- Heads or tails? - I'll do the body in the acid, okay?
正面还是反面
Heads or tails?
正面  我猜正面
Heads. Heads.
还是三局两胜吧
Best two out of three?
唷  唷  唷  148-3369
Yo, yo, yo, 148-3369,
代表阿尔布开克
representing the ABQ.
何事  贱人
What up, biatch?
提示音后留言
Leave it at the tone.
怀特先生  是我  接电话啊
Mr. White, it's me, pick up.
我找不到合适的容器
I got a container question.
喂  怀特先生  接电话啊
Hello? Mr. White, pick up the phone, man!
是我
Yes?
得用哪种塑料  伙计
What kind of plastic, man?
聚乙烯
Polyethylene.
我要怎么分辨
How the hell am I supposed to know that?
我告诉过你
Because I told you.
听着
Look, just...
看底下  会有个三角形
Look at the bottom for a triangle
印着"低密度聚乙烯"
stamped "LDPE".
应该是模压在塑料里的
It should be molded right into the plastic.
恩  恩  低密度聚乙烯  对  找到了
Yeah, yeah, LDPE. Right on, got it.
我不好说  伙计  可这玩意儿看起来很脆弱
But... I don't know, man, this feels kind of flimsy.
随便哪种像样的酸  都能把这腐蚀穿的
Any decent acid's gonna eat right through this.
-氢氟酸就不会  -为啥
- Not hydrofluoric.  - Why not?
听着  你不是
Look, you skipped,
翘了所有课去胡闹了
clowned around or otherwise jerked off
就是去自慰了
to every lecture I ever gave.
在我看来  你的化学学习生涯已经结束了
As far as I'm concerned, your chemistry education is over.
行了  别鸡巴废话了
Oh, okay. Be a dick about it.
你有没有
So, hey, have you...
把活儿干完
Have you done the thing?
恩  我正着手做呢
Yeah, I'm working up to it.
你猜怎么着  我打赌他都没醒过来
You know what? I bet he doesn't even wake up.
即便你现在把他送医院  也不会醒的
Not even if you took him to the hospital right now.
要是我的话
Now, if it was me, I would
就会试着去想
just try and think of
自己只是在帮他忙
I was doing him a favor.
是谁
Who's there?
你他妈的别想玩我  是谁
Don't you fucking play games with me. Who's there?
我可看见你了
Yeah, I see you.
你想要干什么
What are you gonna do?
我要喝水
I need water!
你能不能给我点水喝
Bring me some water, would you?
求你了
Please?
你不喜欢吃面包皮吗
You don't like the crust?
我表弟埃米利奥呢
Where's my cousin Emilio?
他死了吗
He dead?
怀特先生
Hey, Mr. White!
你在抽大麻吗
Are you smoking weed?
我的天啊
Oh, my god!
等等  你抽的是不是我的
Wait a minute. Is that my weed?
怎么回事啊  朋友
What the hell, man?
还真把这当你家了  是不是啊
Make yourself at home, why don't you?
你到底买什么了
So what did you end up buying?
啥都没买
Nothing.
镇上没那种
No store in town sells a plastic bin
大到能装下一个人的塑料箱卖
big enough for a body.
我还真没指望你会去买俩
I don't suppose you could buy two bins...
一个装下半身  一个装上半身
Legs in one, torso in the other?
老天爷
God.
我也从没想过你会阿谀奉承我
I don't suppose you could kiss my ass?
你进展如何
So, how did it go?
你还没搞定吗
So you didn't do it?
还没呢
Not yet.
天啊
God.
该死
Damn.
-我得走了  -啥  别走  给我回来
- I gotta go.  - What? No, come back here!
抱歉  我保证明天搞定
Sorry. I'll do it tomorrow, I promise.
明天吗
Tomorrow?
我跟医生约好了  我得走了
I've got a doctor's appointement, I gotta go.
听着  离他远点
Look, stay away from him.
他醒了
He's awake.
哥们  我们可是抛了硬币的
Hey, man, we flipped a coin.
我们抛了硬币的
We flipped a coin!
胎儿还好吧
We're good?
非常好
We're very good.
我得说  非常之好
We're excellent, I'd say.
你来瞧瞧那张脸
Oh, would you look at that face!
笑一个  小家伙
Smile, peanut!
那么  做好知道性别的准备了吗
So, who's up for knowing?
女孩
Girl.
女孩吗
Girl?
-你确定吗  -非常确定
- You sure?  - Pretty sure.
我能跟你说这是我梦寐以求的吗
Can I tell you this is exactly what I was hoping?
还记得你说过
You remember you said that
等她16岁就可以开始约会了
when she's 16 and starts dating.
真是难以置信啊
Looking fabulous.
我去看看血糖化验做好了没
Let me see if they're done with the
做好的话你们就可以走了
blood sugar, then you can go out of here.
我一会儿回来
I'll be right back.
杰西·平克曼是谁
Who is Jesse Pinkman?
杰西
Jesse...
杰西·平克曼
Jesse Pinkman.
他今早打过电话  沃尔特  别否认
He called just this morning, Walt, please don't deny it.
他空间上说他在怀恩中学读过书
It says on his Myshout page he attended Wynne.
他是不是你的学生
Was he one of your students?
是的  他只是个
Yeah. He was...
谁也不是
Nobody.
他跟你什么关系
Who is he to you?
他干嘛打电话来  有什么不可告人的
Why is he calling? What is this big secret
你们好像在讨论一些
you seem to be discussing with some...
什么关于瘾君子的事情
Druggie burn-out?
昨晚凌晨两点
You don't come home
你才回家
last night until 2 in the morning,
你也没跟我说去了哪
you don't tell me where you been.
你一整夜都呆在卫生间里  沃尔特
You spent the entire night in the bathroom, Walt.
告诉我  你到底怎么了
Tell me what's going on with you.
你不觉得该给我个解释吗
Don't you think you owe me that?
这个杰西·平克曼到底跟你什么关系
Who's this Jesse Pinkman to you?
他卖大麻给我
He sells me pot.
他卖  大麻给你
He sells you... pot?
是的  大麻
Marijuana, yeah.
也没多少
Not a lot.
我是说  我也不知道
I mean, I don't know.
我还挺喜欢的
I kinda like it.
你脑子进水了吗
Are you out of your mind?
你多大了  还是16岁吗
What are you, like 16 years old?
你连襟就是缉毒局的
Your brother-in-law is a DEA agent.
你到底怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
听着  斯凯勒
Look...Skyler...
我只是
I just...
最近有点脱线而已
Haven't quite been myself lately.
是  一点不假  多谢您发现了
Yeah, no shit. Thanks for noticing.
我只是有点脱线而已  但我还是爱你的
I haven't been myself lately, but I love you.
这点从未改变过
Nothing about that has changed.
也不会改变
Nothing ever will.
所以现在呢  我需要的只是
So right now, what I need
你别再管我的闲事
is for you to climb down out of my ass.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
能为我做到吗  亲爱的
Will you do that for me, honey?
好吗  求求你  就这一次
Will you, please, just once,
别再管我的事
get off my ass?
你知道  我会感激涕零的
You know, I'd appreciate it.
我真的会
I really would.
够了
Stop!
15分钟后停笔
Stop in 15 minutes.
你的燕尾服太短了
Your tails are too short.
泰勒  泰勒
Taylor. Taylor.
叫上泰勒继续
Take out Taylor and go on.
8号
No. 8.
只是肉  就一堆肉而已
Just meat, is all. Just a bunch of meat.
老天
Oh, Jesus.
镇定  你要镇定
It's cool, you're cool.
你很好
You're all good, yo.
这儿一切都好
You're all good in the hood.
没事的  就一堆肉而已  你搞得定
It's fine. Just a bunch of meat, come on. You got it.
有人在吗
Excuse me!
Excuse me?
你
You.
就是你
Yes, you.
能跟你谈谈吗
May I talk to you?
这是私人地盘
This is private property!
就几句话  我说了就走
Just a minute. I wanna talk to you.
我没兴趣
No, I'm not interested.
别碰我  不要碰我
Hey, don't touch me! Do not touch me.
好的  不碰你  放心了吧  不会碰你
All right, look, not touching, okay? Not touching here.
女士  不管你推销什么  我是不会买的
Look, lady, whatever you're selling, I ain't buying, yo.
我是斯凯勒·怀特
Well, my name is Skyler White, yo.
我丈夫叫沃尔特·怀特
My husband is Walter White, yo.
他全都告诉我了
He told me everything.
-真的吗  -是的
- Seriously?  - That's right.
你要知道...
And just so you know...
我妹夫是缉毒局探员
My brother-in-law is a DEA agent.
逼不得已的时候
And I will not hesitate to call him.
我会毫不犹豫地告发你
Not if I have to.
明白吗
Understood?
别说我没警告过你
This is your one and only warning.
不许再卖大麻给我丈夫
Do not sell marijuana to my husband.
-好的  -我说到做到
- Okay.  - I mean it.
别再往我家打电话
Don't call our house again.
别再缠着他  不然有你好果子吃
You stay away from him, or you'll be one sorry individual.
听明白了
You got me?
我想是的
I think so, yeah.
大麻  不许再卖给他
No more marijuana.
我明白
I can dig it.
你明白了
You can dig it.
很好
Wonderful.
虽然不关我什么事
Not that it's any of my business,
但你也许该考虑换种活法了
but you might wanna consider a different line of work.
好的
Okay.
一起去你家
"Let's go to your house, yo!
简直太棒了
"Makes perfect sense. Let's...
把你们家统统搞乱
"Let's completely screw up your house
让你一天都待不下去
"So you never wanna spend another night in it."
当然  干嘛不呢
"Sure. You know, why not?"
然后让我找个神经病婊子
"And then, how's about I send
去找你怎么样
over my psycho-bitch off my mind.
让她废了你再吓颇你的胆
"You know, break your balls and threaten you?
老天  那太滑稽了
"God, that'd be hilarious."
还有那个在地下室里的杀手
"And then, the killer in the basement?
也由我全权负责
"The one who's completely my responsabilty.
就让他在那住下吧
"Hell, let's just let him live down there.
我只要管饭就行
"Just, I don't know, make sure to feed him, like...
一日三餐不耽误
"Three times a day."
当然  干嘛不呢
"Sure, why not?
那简直太棒了
"That would be really amazing.
谢谢你给我这个机会
"Thank you so much for the opportunity.
我一直梦想着有一天  化个尸什么的
"I always dreamt about, I don't know, melting bodies."
你有个弟弟在天杀的缉毒局对吧
You got a brother in the goddamned DEA?
你说过你只是路上碰到的
You said you were just doing some ride-along.
你有个弟弟在缉毒局  是不是
Yes or no, do you have a brother in the DEA?
是我连襟
Brother-in-law.
现在我总算松了一口气了
Now there's a load off my mind.
你从哪听来的
Where did you hear that?
你家那疯婆子来数落我的时候
Your freaking wife told me when
亲口说的
she was here all of my shit?
对  就是这样
Yeah, that's right.
我在搬尸的时候差点给她逮到
She almost caught me moving Emilio!
在家里人模狗样的装得不错嘛
Good job in wearing the pants in the family.
为什么跟她说我卖大麻给你了
And why did you go and tell her I was selling you weed?
不管怎么说  总比承认我在
Because somehow, it seemed preferable to admitting
制冰毒而且还杀了人强吧
that I cook crystal meth and killed a man.
是我想的那个吗
Is that what I think it is?
对  我吸了  有意见啊
Yeah, it is. I smoked a bowl, so what?
我的地盘我做主
My house, my rules.
不不  别这么看着我  我都搞定了
Hey, no, no! Don't give me that, okay? I held up my end.
把埃米利奥处理掉了
I already took care of Emilio.
就在你闲荡  搞基的时候
You're still diddling around, trying to get your nut up.
胡说  我还有份糟透了的工作要做
Well, boo-hoo. I have the truly awful job here.
你懂什么叫糟透了吗你  你懂吗
You wanna talk awful? You wanna go there?
拖个两百磅重臭气熏天的尸体上楼试试
Try dragging 200 pounds of stink up a flight of stairs.
把他弄进浴缸我容易吗
I barely got him in the bathtub!
浴缸  什么
Bathtub? What...
-你说"浴缸"是什么意思  -还有件事
- What do you mean, "Bathtub"?  - That's another thing,
你干嘛让我找遍全城
Why you got me running around town,
找什么愚蠢的塑料桶
trying to find some stupid piece of plastic,
我那浴缸用起来就十分足够了
when I have a perfectly good tub I can use?
我的天
Oh, God.
抱歉  你刚问我什么来着
I'm sorry, what were you asking me?
想起来了
Oh, yes.
我让你去找什么"愚蠢的"塑料容器
That stupid plastic container I asked you to buy.
看到了吧  氢氟酸不会腐蚀塑料
You see, hydrofluoric acid won't eat through plastic.
但却能溶解金属  岩石
It will however dissolve metal, rock,
玻璃  还有陶瓷
glass, ceramic.
就像现在这样
So there's that.